Sofía Fernández Moreno

DevOps Junior Born 1994 in Jaén



About me

Hi, my name is Sofía Fernández Moreno. I'm just about the most boring type of person you could possibly imagine. I like collecting logs with SIEM monitoring and living in the new era of the Cloud. I am not a robot. Please hire

Also proficient in developing CI/CD pipelines, Configuration Management Tools and deployments over large infrastructure.

Skills

Bash, Python, C++, Ruby, Groovy

Docker, Docker-Compose, Docker-Swarm, Kubernetes

CI/CD: Jenkins, Github Actions

Pentesting

Social Enginering

Nmap, Wireshark, Kali Linux Tools

Penetration testing

OSINT Tools

Experience configuring NGINX, Apache, Redis, SSL and TLS certificates, PostgresSQL

LDAP and Active Directory

Cloud: GCP, Azure, AWS

Contact



chui274@gmail.com

655760279

sofiafernandezmoreno.github.io

in sofiafernandezmoreno

sofiafernandezmoreno



Experience

Administrative and web designer

STA Villacarrillo

June 2017 - September 2017

Performing office tasks, such as managing the CRM of the company, adapting data in SEO. In addition to the maintenance of the website of the

Internship trainee

Euroinnova Business School S.L

November 2018 - May 2019

Work in computer and web development department, carrying out support tasks in the computer department in the company such as programming, requirements analysis, data storage, etc.

E-learning Content Designer

INNOFORMA ELEARNING TECHNOLOGIES, S.L.

May 2019 - September 2019

Expert in creation of formative content of the branch of Computing and New Technologies.

DevOps Junior

SOCIAL NETWORK LOYCUS S.A.

September 2019 - Now

Management, monitoring, alert and administration of the tools used within the life cycle of the applications and the platform.

DevOps Engineer

ALTEN

June 2020 - Now

Management, monitoring, alert and administration k8s infraestructure in Airbus Client



Education

MASTER SECURITY INFORMATION

November 2019 - July 2020

Universidad Europea de Madrid

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

September 2015 - September 2019

Universidad de Granada

Projects

Análisis y monitorización de SECURITY SYSTEM aplicaciones a través de plugins con Naemon

Docker, Naemon

Final Degree Project vinculated with DevOps World.

Arduino, C

Project of security system based on Arduino.



Certificates and Courses

Course of computer forensics

Course of Programming Web Java EE Indra



English (B1) French (A2)

Spanish (Native)